It's crazy!
What do you want me to say?
I'm trying here, Jo!
[Download Movie 480p & 720p Just on Mkvking.com]
Just...
You tell me what you need me to say.
The fact that you don't know what to say,
that's the problem.
You know what it is?
They just never liked me.
No, that's not true.
Really, 'cause your Dad's sitting there
offering me wine as if he didn't know.
And your Mom's just sittin'
on the other side of the table
shootin' me dirty looks.
Maybe she was upset
because the turkey was getting cold, Ray.
What do I got to do with the turkey?
It took so long for you to get us there.
I was driving 55.
I drove the speed limit.
Is that the problem, Jo?
I am a safe driver.
Okay.
Look, why don't we just go home
and do Thanksgiving all over again,
all right?
Just the three of us. Our way.
We could get pizza. Peri loves pizza.
And then we can be thankful
for each other.
Yeah?
We need to stop kidding ourselves, Ray.
We're just...
broken.
We have been for a long time.
I don't know why you would say that.
I would talk to you about it
if we ever actually talked,
but we don't.
That's not fair.
I work,
and sometimes I just like to... think.
But you don't fight for anything anymore.
You used to.
What about us?
Who do you want me to be?
I want you to be yourself.
The guy that I married six years ago.
The guy that I used to laugh with
and... and... and dream with and...
I'm still that guy, Jo.
I'm in a patch, and I admit it,
but I love you, okay?
And maybe I should just say it more often,
'cause I love you...
Ray!
Jesus.
- It's not working.
- Okay.
It broke, Mommy, and the songs won't play.
Let me see it, baby.
Probably the batteries.
Right, Daddy?
Yeah. Probably the batteries.
You brought extras, right? I told you.
I left them on the... the counter.
Daddy will get you some more batteries,
all right, sweetie?
Hey, I have an idea.
Let's play I Spy.
- Blech.
- Blech?
- What do you mean, "blech"?
- Why don't we sing a song?
- Let's start with one obvious one.
- Let's sing a song.
- "Shake It Off."
- I Spy...
Hm. That's a good one too,
but I'm thinking more "Sing a Rainbow."
Okay.
- Maybe it's gotten a little babyish, Ray.
- One,
two... ♪ Red and yellow ♪
♪ And pink and green ♪
♪ Orange and purple and blue ♪
♪ I can sing a rainbow ♪
♪ Sing a rainbow ♪
- ♪ Sing a rainbow for you ♪
- ♪ Listen with your eyes ♪
♪ Listen with your ears ♪
♪ And sing everything you see ♪
♪ I can sing a rainbow ♪
♪ Sing a rainbow ♪
♪ Sing a rainbow with me ♪
Daddy?
Yeah?
I gotta go potty.
What, right now?
- I gotta go.
- Can you hold it?
No.
Okay, I'll pull over
at the next rest stop, and then we'll...
tinkle. Okay?
Maybe they'll have batteries.
Mommy, come on! I have to go!
All right, baby.
Lean forward.
Remember, we don't touch anything
that we don't have to in there.
Can you get me a Coke, please?
- Yeah.
- I don't know why, but I'm parched.
And can I get a four-pack
of AA batteries, please?
And two of these, please.
Okay.
No plastic.
Okay, just... just the coffee
and the Coke and the...
Thank you.
Did you get batteries?
They didn't have any.
Mommy, my compact! Where is it?
I don't know,
why are you asking me, Per?
Because it's gone!
What... Did you check
on the seat under your bum?
Yes, it's not there.
- I had it in the ladies' room, remember?
- You check your pocket?
In the ladies' room?
Okay. Well, I will go check
in the ladies' room.
But if I find it in there,
you don't get to touch it
until we get home, okay?
Okay.
Will you check in the back,
under the seats?
Yeah.
Daddy, check the seats.
Come on.
Up, up, up.
Here we go. I got ya.
All right.
Right, just stay right there.
Peri, where is the...
It's a pigsty back here.
Where am I even meant to begin,
you know?
God damn it!
Daddy.
I just...
This shi...
This is gonna stain. You know?
What if I wanted to resell this car?
Can't even do that.
I guess this is just the cherry
on the cake, this is.
Come on...
Peri, there's no sign of the thing.
Daddy.
Daddy!
- Daddy!
- What? What?
Peri, don't move.
All right, don't be scared.
Just stay right there.
Hey! Dog! Go on!
Hey! Go on.
Go on. Go on, move.
No, no, Peri, not you. J-Just stay there.
Peri, don't move.
Don't move. Don't move, okay?
Go on!
Go on, get!
Don't move.
Peri, stop.
It's gonna be okay.
I'm just gonna scare him.
No!
Sorry, Mr. Monroe. She's gone.
They're both gone.
Ray?
Uh, Ray? Ray?
Ray? Ray!
Ray! Ray! Ray!
Ray! Ray!
My baby!
Daddy.
Peri? Baby? Baby?
Oh, my... Oh, my God. Baby?
Baby? Baby?
- Joanne, don't move her.
- She's okay. She's okay. She's okay.
Put her down.
She's okay. She's okay.
There you go.
I'm right here. I'm right here.
You hurt?
I don't think so.
Okay. Well, there doesn't seem to be
any scratches or bruises.
Ray, she needs a doctor.
I know what I'm doin'.
- Ray...
- I'm gonna pick you up, all right?
- Ow!
- Hold on. What is it? What is it?
- My arm, Daddy. It hurts.
- This arm?
I think it's broken.
Let's try again.
Nice and slow.
Don't hurt me, Daddy.
I would never hurt you, sweetie.
I would never hurt you.
Gentle, Daddy.
- Gentle, Ray.
- Okay. It's all right. Up we go.
Here we go.
Daddy's got you.
Here we go. Yeah, here we go.
Here we are.
Here we go.
Shh. It's okay.
I'm calling 911.
- Don't bother. I'll drive.
- Ray...
I saw a hospital sign a few miles back.
By the time that ambulance gets here,
we'd have gotten her to help.
Are you sure?
Joanne, I got this.
We're gonna stay awake
until we get to the hospital.
Daddy's gonna get us there
real fast. Okay?
Move.
Hurry, Ray, hurry.
Nearly there.
Oh, come on, come on, come on.
Oh!
Ray. Hurry.
Ray?
Ray.
Ray!
Okay.
There it is! There it is. There it is.
Okay. Daddy's got us.
- Almost there.
- We're there.
All right, right.
I'll go get a wheelchair.
Nah, I'm gonna carry her. Okay, sweetie.
I'll go get us checked in. All right?
I won't be long, sweetie.
Okay.
We've been waiting for hours.
What's taking so long?
I understand.
- He's in pain.
- I apologize.
I'm gonna find someone
for you here, right...
Ray.
This is gonna take a sec.
You should take a seat,
make her more comfortable.
She's really hurting.
I know. I'll take care of it.
Okay.
So it doesn't matter
that the address has changed,
That's okay? All right.
Excuse me. I need a doctor.
There's been an accident.
- Do you mind?
- Take a seat. We'll be with you shortly.
- Hang on, it's my daughter.
- No!
- We think she broke her arm.
- Sir, take a seat, and I assure you...
- She's in a lot of pain!
- We'll get you checked in
as soon as possible.
- Take a seat.
- I just need to see someone.
Enough. Sit down.
Wait your turn. Please.
I'm sure it won't be long.
I heard her, Ray.
Mm-hmm. Just stay calm.
I'll be calm
when a doctor sees our daughter.
It's okay. Shh, shh, shh.
Daddy's gonna take care of us.
What do you want me to do?
You want me to kick down the doors
- and drag a doctor out here?
- Yes.
That I'd like to see.
Do something.
Do something, Ray.
Sir?
How can I help you, sir?
Yeah, I really need to see that doctor,
right now.
I understand.
But as I told you before, sir,
there are other patients ahead of you.
Can you just squeeze us in?
She's sick.
She doesn't know what's going on.
- Did you sign in?
- What?
It moves a lot faster if you sign in.
Y-You told me to sit down.
Mr. Fellows? Dale Fellows.
Hi, Dale. How are you feeling today?
He has a sharp pain in his stomach.
Bit of paperwork first,
and we'll get him admitted.
Would you happen to know
what Dale's blood type is?
B positive.
Another one.
Maybe 15 years old.
B positive.
Let Dr. Berthram know.
Dr. Berthram...
Please go back to your seat, sir.
I'll let you know
when a doctor becomes available.
- We're on the list now.
- Shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh.
She's sleeping.
Okay.
Here, hold this.
It's so hot in here.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to...
bite your head off earlier.
It's okay. Uh...
We're gonna be fine.
Thank you.
For what?
For getting us here so fast.
I just did what needed to be done.
- Well, you missed your calling.
- Yeah?
Driving NASCAR.
Ah, man, I missed that.
Missed what?
Just... laughing with you.
Mm...
You okay?
My head is just...
mm, like, throbbing.
I mean, you're probably dehydrated.
I can fix that.
There you go.
- Thank you.
- Who are they?
They are the ones who fight
and don't give up,
keeping our families safe.
Sons, husbands, fathers. Our heroes.
Monroe. Ray Monroe.
Yeah, go on.
Can I see
your driver's license and insurance card?
- All this information is correct?
- Yeah.
Your occupation?
I work at Craft Home Improvement.
He's the assistant manager
for the kitchen
and bathroom design center.
Has Peri had any prior surgeries?
Allergies?
Yes. She reacts to penicillin.
Her skin breaks out in a rash.
Any history of mental illness
in the family?
No.
Drugs? Alcoholism?
I'm a recovering alcoholic.
How long is this going to take?
Just a couple of minutes.
Your insurance records show
a prior dependent, Abby Monroe.
My first wife is deceased.
And this happened...?
Eight years ago. Why is this relevant?
There's just an overlap in your plan
that your PPO never fixed.
Were you at the same employer then?
No. I was self-employed and, um...
- Listen...
- And you're married?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Of course, yeah.
- How many years?
- Six.
Honestly, how long is this gonna take?
We're almost finished.
Would you like Peri listed
for organ donation?
No.
Can I convince you to reconsider?
The number of children
on the transplant list is...
Not now, please.
What is your daughter's blood type?
Your blood types?
O, I think.
That's all right.
We can crossmatch later if necessary.
- Why would that be necessary?
- Last one.
The state requires me to ask
if everything is safe in the household.
- Really?
- Ray...
With these types of injuries, sir,
I am mandated by law.
Okay, but this was an accident
at a construction site.
Ray... Yes, we're safe.
Our household...
- is safe.
- Mommy?
All right, then. We're done.
I'll get a nurse to take you back. Oh.
My arm, it still hurts.
- What?
- I know, sweetheart.
Sir, it looks like we don't take
your type of medical insurance here.
- Ray...
- I'm sorry.
If you call your provider,
they can give you a list of qualified...
A list? I don't need a list.
I need a doctor.
This hospital's admission policy
requires proof of coverage.
Whatever it takes, I'll cover it. Okay?
You do take cash here?
You got an ATM?
You take cash?
I will have to check.
Excuse me.
This is insane.
I can't believe this, can you?
She's sitting there going...
"Your shoe size?"
Mommy?
- He doesn't have...
- Did you find my compact?
We didn't, sweetheart,
but I'm gonna buy you another one soon.
Everything's fine, Mr. Monroe.
- You're good to go.
- Fantastic.
Nurse Anne will get you situated.
Okay.
- Hi, is this Peri?
- Yes.
- We'll get you taken care of right away.
- Yes, another one.
- Come on, baby.
- Sit in the wheelchair for me?
A walk-in. Six-year-old female,
unknown blood type.
Let Dr. Berthram know.
Kirkbride serves three counties,
so it can get quite busy.
And EMS just brought in
a couple of head traumas
- so it's backed us up a bit.
- Yeah, I saw that. What happened?
A couple of teenagers. Head-on collision.
It was a drunk driver.
That's horrible. They all right?
As I understand it,
it's touch-and-go.
Do you have to do that?
He's in a lot of pain.
I just need to know
where he's hurting, okay?
Okay, sweetheart.
There you are. Okay.
Doctor will be right in.
Hey, baby.
Hey, just keep that arm in your lap,
lay back on the pillow.
- Won't be long.
- Better not be...
or I'm gonna break somebody's arm.
Not mine, I hope.
Hi. I'm Dr. Berthram.
Hi.
- You must be...
- Peri.
- I'm sorry, I didn't mean to...
No, no, no, it's quite all right.
Sometimes I've gotta crack
a few heads myself around here
to get anything done.
So, Perry Mason,
what can we do for ya?
Monroe. Peri Monroe.
Oh! Yes. I see it now.
Yes. Peri. And that's P-E-R-I?
It's short for Periwinkle.
Isn't that sweet?
It's my mommy's favorite shell.
Okay, sweetheart.
Let's let the nice doctor do his job.
It's all right, I'm not that nice.
So...
what's the story, young lady?
I fell.
Oh, dear. Yeah.
Well, sooner or later, everybody does.
Right, Dad?
So, Peri,
I'm gonna see how that arm is doing,
and if anything hurts,
anything at all,
I want you to let me know. Deal?
- Deal.
- Okay.
Where did this happen?
- It's a gas station a few miles from here.
- We're on our way to Minneapolis.
Visiting Grandma and Grandpa
for Thanksgiving, I bet.
Uh-huh.
- All right, so you were at a gas station?
- Yup.
Yeah, off Route 20.
I know. I'm sorry.
Uh, there was a dog, and it scared her.
A dog?
Uh, it was just an accident.
You didn't say anything about a dog.
Did that hurt when I touched here?
- Yeah, I know, sweetie. That's an ouchie.
- Uh, it doesn't matter, she just fell.
And I nearly had you, didn't I?
So, sweetheart, when you fell,
did you hit your head, Peri? You did?
You know, you are a real trooper.
You think it's broken?
I think the swelling is consistent
with a fracture along the distal radius,
but we'll get an...
We'll get an X-ray to confirm that.
- She need a cast?
- We're going to put her in...
You're a brave girl. Yeah.
I don't think
they're gonna have to amputate.
- Yeah.
- I'll tell you one thing.
In a few weeks,
this arm is gonna be as good as new.
Now, look at my shoulder.
Peri, look at my shoulder.
That's right. My shoulder.
That's right. Uh-huh.
Most beautiful eyes I've ever seen.
Now, Peri, Nurse Anne is gonna come
and give you some medicine for the pain.
I gotta talk to Mommy and Daddy here
for a minute.
Um... ibuprofen. Check vitals please.
Uh, this way, guys.
Okay, baby.
I'm concerned
about a possible head injury.
There's no reason for alarm.
It's just I'm not seeing
the pupil dilation that I like.
Since you're traveling,
I'd like to do a CAT scan
just to rule out anything internal.
But she seems fine.
And I would agree with you,
but on the off chance
that it's bleeding around the brain,
what we would call a subdural hematoma,
now that can be quite serious.
A head injury like that could lead
to confusion, seizures,
even the possibility of slipping
into a coma.
We've... We've heard enough. Do it.
Yeah, but you need to know...
it is a costly procedure.
I would do anything for my family,
so you do what you have to do.
Make sure she's okay.
That's a wise choice.
You know, that's a pretty nasty
little scrape you have yourself.
- Should I take a look?
- It's nothin'. I'm a tough guy.
Okay, well, give me a minute
to get things in motion for Peri.
Yeah.
She's all right, isn't she?
Yeah. Yeah, you heard him.
It's nothing.
It's just a precaution.
It's better to be safe, right?
We'll be fine.
We will, Ray.
Wow. Look... look at that.
This goes over your head
right here.
You're being so brave.
We're almost done,
and we get to go home soon.
He's going down to the lower level
for an appendectomy.
It looks like you're feeling better.
Hey, maybe we should get a motel
like the old days
and pick up the drive tomorrow.
That's the best idea I've heard all day.
My head is killing me.
Maybe they have a hot tub.
Hello, Peri.
Nurse Anne and I got this for you
for being the number one patient
of the day.
Oh! Ah, look at that. Thank you.
That's so sweet.
No problem.
- I hope you feel better.
- I'm Bruce.
And I'm gonna take you downstairs
so we can take a little peek
inside that little noggin of yours. Okay?
- Okay.
You know, you must have made
quite an impression on Dr. Berthram.
He does not crack a smile
for just anybody.
Yeah, she's a real charmer.
Dad here must have to keep a shotgun handy
to chase off all the boys, am I right?
All right, keep your arms and legs
inside the vehicle.
Mm-hmm.
So, this is a...
a more restricted part of the hospital.
I can only take one visitor down
with a patient to the lower level.
- Okay.
- Sorry about that.
Hey, you go.
You sure?
Yeah, I'll be fine.
Okay.
Hey. I'm gonna wait right here for you
when you get out.
Actually, you might want to wait
out front.
Yeah, scans can take a while,
especially if they're backed up.
Okay, then.
I'll book that motel.
Daddy, can I have a pizza?
Yeah.
- With extra cheese.
- Extra cheese.
Yeah.
I love you, Daddy.
I love you, sweetheart.
You did good.
Okay. Okay, okay. We'll see you in a few.
Yeah.
Next year, we fly.
How about next year, we stay home?
Daddy!
Next time, we fly.
Hey, buddy, you all right?
You were talkin' in your sleep.
Well, suppose somebody came along
and offered you
a million dollars for your life.
Would you take it?
John, don't even talk like that.
Do you mean I'll be... dead?
No, I'm fine.
Well, not me.
I wouldn't take it.
Your life is worth
more than a million dollars,
so don't bet it on getting around
in a car in order to save
a couple of minutes.
The gamble isn't worth it.
The stakes are too high
for what you can possibly get out of it.
- It still hurts.
- Excuse me.
I think my baby has an infection
or something. He won't stop crying.
Okay, how long has that been going on for?
A couple of days.
Okay, um, well,
I'm gonna get you to sign this form.
If you'll just take a seat, sir.
Thank you.
How may I help you?
Do you know how much longer it's gonna be?
Sir, I'm gonna need
a little more information than that.
My daughter, Peri Monroe,
she went for a CAT scan with my wife.
Okay, so she checked in before?
Yeah.
All right, morning shift
would have taken care of that.
I don't have the imaging schedule,
but it can take a little while.
Yeah. They told me that, I just...
You know, I know my kid.
She's gonna be hungry
I just wanna check on her.
As I said, sir,
I don't have that information here.
It's been hours.
And if you just take a seat,
I'm sure she'll be out shortly.
Cardiology, 54-12. Cardiology.
I'd like to speak with Dr. Berthram.
Dr. Berthram has left for the day.
But he was helping us.
I understand,
but he would have passed his cases
to the other doctor on duty.
I can have the nurse's station
pass along a message to the on-duty,
- All right?
- Yeah.
If you'll just give me a moment.
- Oh, no!
- Truck!
I lived it again and again,
like in slow motion...
We're gonna hit it!
It's enough to drive you nuts, isn't it?
Sorry?
The wait.
I've seen you sitting over there.
My husband went in at 6:00 a.m.
Melanoma.
Pretty simple procedure.
Now it's almost dinnertime.
Hurry up and wait.
Hurry up and pay.
Sometimes they hope
we all just die in the meantime.
Uh, what are you in for?
Nothing.
Call a doctor for Tommy.
Call an ambulance.
Excuse me.
What's that? It's...
Hi, how may I help you?
My daughter?
Oh, right, yes. I did leave word, sir,
but I haven't heard back yet.
Can you check again now, please?
Okay, what was her name again?
Peri Monroe.
Monroe. M-U-N?
No, M-O-N-R-O-E.
Okay, I have several Monroes here,
but I'm not seeing a Peri Monroe.
Could she be under another name?
I signed in.
I signed in on the clipboard, right?
It's right... It's right here.
Yeah, but that gets thrown out
at the end of each shift.
It would all be in the system by now,
but I'm not seeing a "Peri Monroe."
That's crazy 'cause we were admitted.
You know,
you asked us for all this information.
Yes, but the patient's file
is always under the patient's name,
and I'm not seeing a "Peri Monroe."
She is a patient.
She's a patient of Dr. Berthram's.
- Yeah, he saw her.
- Dr. Berthram has left for the evening.
Yeah, I know that! You told me that!
Sir, there's no need...
to raise your voice.
Check again. When we came in,
in late morning, we did all this,
and then they took her down
to the CAT scan.
Okay, maybe they put it
under your insurance number.
Can I get your card?
You wouldn't take my insurance.
You said that I could pay cash.
- Cash?
- Yeah, all worked out.
The woman who admitted us,
she asked. They said it was fine.
I've just never heard it being done
that way before.
Yeah, I don't care about that
because I don't make the rules. All right?
Let's ask her.
Let's ask the woman that checked us in.
She's already gone.
Then let's ask the ER, all right?
Because there was a nurse named Anne,
there was an orderly, his name was Bruce.
There's been a full shift rotation.
I just want to see my wife and daughter,
and they're back there.
Unless I can identify you
with a patient, I...
It's been a long day,
and I just need you to call down
to where they do the CAT scans
and see if there's a woman
and a six-year-old kid still there,
and whether they're waiting,
or if they want to come home.
Can you do that, please?
You're... You're bleeding.
Hi, this is the main desk.
Oh, hi, Tim.
You better stop,
or I'll make you live up to that.
Um, anyway, I'm just calling
about a little girl.
She came up for a scan.
Late morning.
I know, I know,
but can you check for me, please?
You're bad.
Bye.
I'm sorry, sir, there hasn't been a scan
since nine o'clock this morning,
and it was for a 62-year-old woman's hip.
So what are you telling me?
I'm sorry, they're not here.
What? What? You lost my family?
Maybe you're at the wrong hospital.
I've been sitting there all day.
Maybe they left
before you got here.
Why would they do that?
- We came together.
- I'm sorry, sir. Sir! They're not here.
Would you please excuse me
so I can deal
with the gentleman behind you?
- What are you saying?
- Hi, how may I help you?
My wife's been sitting over there
for two hours.
It's just going to be
a little bit longer.
Uh, excuse me, sir!
You can't go back there!
Drew, that man,
he shouldn't be back there.
Call security.
What the hell? Do you mind?
- I'm so sorry, I'm just looking for...
- Hey!
- You're not supposed to be back here.
- Okay. Okay. Okay.
- Hey! Hey!
- All right. Enough.
- Drew, what's going on?
- This guy just rushed in from up front.
Just... uh, my family's back here.
The receptionist, she wouldn't...
I don't give a shit, pal. Just calm down.
What is going on here?
I'm just looking for my wife and daughter.
Joanne and Peri Monroe.
Are they patients here?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah. My daughter is.
That's what I'm trying to explain.
All right, all right,
let's all just take it easy. Okay?
I'm Dr. Lucado. And you?
Me, I'm Ray Monroe.
Okay, Ray...
why don't you tell me
what all this fuss is about.
Well, we came in earlier,
and my daughter saw Dr. Berthram, he...
- She had a potentially fractured arm.
- Okay, was she released?
No, no, no. She...
He was worried about a head injury.
He took her to the CAT scan.
Joanne went with her.
- That's the last time I saw her.
- This was when?
Hours ago.
- Monroe?
- M... M-O-N-R-O-E.
What a day, huh?
Got the whole day in front of me here,
and I'm not finding any Monroe.
Well, that's insane 'cause, you know,
we were here.
We were right... right there.
- All right...
- So was she. So was she.
She... She knows me.
She helped us. Ask her! Ask her!
Okay. Just calm down.
Anne, can I see you for a second?
- Yes?
- Have you seen this man before?
Yes.
- He was here on my earlier shift.
- See?
He was treated for a head injury.
A head injury?
That's not true.
I see.
Why are you lying?
That is a pretty nasty contusion
you have there.
You're lying.
- Ray, I need you to calm down.
- Just leave me alone.
- Ray, calm down.
- Stop calling me "Ray."
You don't even know me.
What have you done to my family?
- Where's my wife, huh?
- Calm down!
Where'd you take my family?
- Get off me!
- Calm down!
- Droperidol. Five milligrams.
Get off me!
- Hold him still.
- Calm down!
Hold him still.
Ah!
Settle down!
We cannot have you disrupting
this hospital.
Hold him in four. I'll call upstairs.
Oh, God.
Yeah.
- Hey. Hey.
- Hold tight.
- Get up on there.
- Get off me. Get off.
Yeah, you gonna keep swinging?
Give me your hand. Give me your hand!
Please, please. You don't need them.
- You gonna behave yourself?
- Yeah.
It's okay.
I'm sorry. It's just...
Just a little confused, is all.
Wipe your eyes with this.
You're gonna be locked up in here
until the doctor can figure out
what you need, okay?
Lay down, let the sedative do its work.
Yeah, sure.
No...
Come on, wake up.
Wake up.
Wake up! Where is it?
Come on! Where is it?
All right. Hey.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Come on.
Okay. Come on.
Three, two, one...
Oh, my God!
Call security!
Hey!
Hey. You remember me?
You remember my daughter, Peri Monroe?
Your dad must have to keep
a shotgun handy
to chase off all the boys,
am I right?
Hey! Hey! You!
Oh! Hey!
Oh!
Hey!
Oh, shit.
Whoa!
Get out of the way!
Fuck!
Ah!
- Hey, Jeff. Jeff?
- Fuck.
Did you get him?
Yeah, Frank, he got away.
All right, what do you want me to do?
Let reception know
in case he thinks he's comin' back.
Holy shit.
Oh, God.
Ah!
We had a noise complaint.
Two white males in a vacant lot.
Looks like they may be getting high...
- Hey! Stop!
- Oh, Jesus. What the fuck?
Help me! They've taken my family!
They just took 'em, just took my family.
They won't let me see them.
Step back. Calm down.
Then they gave me this shot and this drug,
and they kind of knocked me out.
- Relax.
- Maybe they gave the same thing
to my wife,
'cause I don't know what's happening.
- I don't know what happened.
- Calm down!
- I... I'm calm. I'm calm.
- What are you talkin' about?
She's... My daughter's in there,
and she's only six.
Is this a custody thing?
No. We came here to get help,
and now they're saying that she didn't...
That she she never came here.
All right? They've done something.
They've done something,
and they're trying to cover it up.
What happened to your hand?
This? They locked me in a room.
I had to break out.
- All right. Can I see some ID, please?
- Yeah.
Here.
Here. That's them. That's them.
That's my wife.
That's... That's my daughter.
We were... It was Thanksgiving.
We were just going home,
and we stopped at this gas station,
and she falls over, she hurts herself,
and that's why we came here.
That's why I know they're still in there.
Okay. What are their names?
Joanne and Peri Monroe.
And I'm... I'm Ray.
Okay.
- You're gonna help me?
- All right.
Why don't we go inside
and see if we can sort this out?
- Would you please?
- Okay.
Come on.
Hey, it's the front desk.
Send somebody over here now.
It's him.
Hey, we just dropped off that OD.
Yes, what can I do for you?
Okay, so, now we have this man here
who says that you all
are holding his family against their will.
- You stay away from me.
- That's ridiculous.
That's the guy.
That's the one that put me in the room,
and he held me against my will.
- You know this guy?
- Yeah.
All right, well,
he's saying that you roughed him up
- and that you injected him with drugs.
- Yep.
No, he was in earlier and acting a fool,
so the on-call doc gave him a sedative.
- That's what happened.
- You're a liar.
I'm not lying.
Why aren't you arresting his ass?
Calm down. Let us handle this.
Now, where did you last see
your wife and daughter?
It was in the emergency ward,
it was ward nine.
It was just through those doors.
I can't believe you guys
are buying into this bullshit.
I mean, he's a fuckin' head case!
Look at him.
Want to take us to ward nine...
Jeff?
Today, please.
Now, your chest X-rays
show a slight infiltration
in the right lower front lobe
of your lungs...
Doctor.
Now do you want to tell me
where my wife and daughter are?
- They should've locked you up!
- We'll handle this.
He slipped out.
Can you answer this man's question?
He says that his wife and daughter
are missing in the hospital.
The answer is, I don't know.
According to our nursing staff,
Mr. Monroe came in alone,
- wishing to be seen for a head injury.
- Peri was admitted.
Where's her file? Where's her file?
Can we take this to my office, please?
Gotta be a record somewhere, right?
For patients admitted.
I wasn't on call then.
Sometimes files get misplaced
or they get filed under the wrong name.
Maybe it wasn't entered into the system.
These things happen.
You're full of shit.
You should call that Dr. Berthram,
all right?
He sent Peri to get the CAT scan,
and that was the last time I saw him.
Call... Dr. Berthram.
This is ridiculous.
Where's Dr. Berthram?
He went off call. He's probably at home.
Well, if he can sort this out,
it's probably worth giving him a call,
right?
Right?
Call Gabe.
Where do you do the CAT scans?
Um... our imaging lab's
on the third floor.
Okay.
Take us up there please.
Take them up to three.
Hang on.
The CAT scans are downstairs.
- No, our imaging lab's on the third floor.
- No, no, no.
No, I saw them get in an elevator
and go down.
He's obviously confused.
Our lab is on three.
Can you take us up there, please?
This computer keeps a log of usage.
There's date, time, and duration.
You can see this machine
was used at 9:07 a.m.
for a duration lasting exactly 29 minutes.
And that was the last time.
Can you see this clearly, Mr. Monroe?
Yeah, it doesn't prove anything.
It proves no one had a scan
at the time you say
your daughter was here.
- Makes sense.
- Excuse me.
You can see this, right?
Yeah, she wasn't here,
because they never brought her here.
She didn't have a CAT scan.
They just took her somewhere else.
Where?
I don't know.
And why?
You're the detective, you figure it out.
I just know that there's something wrong
with this place.
Dr. Berthram,
who was attending this morning,
will be here shortly.
Good. Maybe he can clear all this up.
Oh, I certainly hope so.
- And there you go.
- Thanks.
- What's your name, baby?
- Anne.
Hmm. So, Anne... double shifts?
Single gal's gotta make a living.
Yes, she does.
You ever sleep?
What time you get off tonight?
Okay, well, this is him. Ray Monroe.
Found this in the trash out front.
It's the morning sign-in list.
Here's my name. There's my name.
Ray, it's... it's your name.
- I signed in for Peri.
- No, you signed in for yourself.
What's going on, Aaron?
Anne said something
about missing patients.
- You know me, right? Remember?
- All right, back off.
All right?
You saw my little girl, all right?
You... You treated her arm. You... You...
- Do you remember this man?
- Tell 'em!
Tell them, please!
I do. He was here earlier today.
- Yes! Yes!
- All right.
And what were the circumstances?
We have been all through this...
I'm talking to Dr. Berthram.
- What were the circumstances?
- Uh...
He was, um...
He was a walk-in,
and one of our doctors, Bruce Volk,
um, he examined him.
He told Anne
that he had been in a car accident.
Uh... Uh...
His behavior seemed rather... erratic.
Dr. Volk asked me to take a look.
So I suggested maybe doing a head CT,
which he refused.
He insisted on going back out
to the lobby to wait for his wife.
- Wh... What was her name?
- Abby.
Abby was her name.
Thought you said
your wife's name was Joanne.
- It is.
- Then who's Abby?
She's my first wife.
Where's Abby now?
She's dead.
She died.
She had nothing to do
with Joanne and Peri.
Joanne and Peri?
Who he claims is his current wife
and child.
This is real.
This is Joanne, and this is Peri.
Periwinkle. You remember?
Because that's Joanne's favorite shell.
And that's my family, and I love them.
What does your first wife have to do
- with any of this?
- Nothin'.
You got Abby's name
from the insurance information, right?
And you're just using it
against me to make me look crazy,
when, in reality,
you've kidnapped my family,
and you've done something to 'em.
All right, enough. Enough.
Okay, there's a simple enough way
to confirm or deny
any of this guy's bullshit.
Right there.
This is today's waiting room feed.
What time did you say
you came in with your family?
Late morning.
So, we'll start at 9:00 a.m.
Work our way forward from there
until we see you.
Stop. Stop.
Go back.
Okay, this is me coming in,
and Joanne was carrying Peri behind me.
All right, there I am. Right.
This is where she said wait.
Um, I went back to the seating area.
What are those?
Those little glitches?
It's an older system.
Records 30 seconds out of every minute,
so there's gonna be gaps.
That's pretty convenient.
- Well, where's your family?
- They're right there. Just...
Can you... They're under the camera.
You can't see where they're sitting
'cause of the chairs.
You got a better angle?
The ones you see are the ones
that are workin' out there.
Just fast forward, fast forward.
Stop.
All right, there I am coming back.
That's after Peri went for the CAT scan.
Yeah.
Never saw you go in with 'em, though.
Your security system is shit.
You've got nothing of my family going in.
- Excuse me.
- This is just shit!
Do you have any footage
from inside the ER?
We don't record
in the treatment areas.
Uh, legal reasons, patient privacy.
Is Dr. Jacobs on call?
Check the hallways.
Check the hallways. Check 'em, all right?
You have better camera placement
in the hall.
We're gonna be here all fuckin' night.
- Search the hospital!
- Okay, that's not happening.
First, we would need a warrant.
Then we would need probable cause,
and there's nothing on that video
that proves anyone is even missing.
You think that I'm faking?
You think I'm making them up?
I showed you the picture!
That could be anybody.
Your sister, niece.
I mean,
the person you keep talking about is Abby.
I don't keep talking about Abby.
You keep talking about Abby.
Come on.
Come on, Ray. You got this.
The cashier
at the service station where Peri fell,
she saw us together.
There's a Gas and Go,
it's a couple of miles from here. Ask her.
- Ask her.
- Uh-huh.
- I'll see if I can track her down.
- Thank you.
Okay.
Mr. Monroe,
I think we found someone back in the ward
that can help us clear everything up.
Let's go.
Let's go, then.
Call if you need backup.
She's already here.
It's Peri's.
This is Peri's scarf.
Jo gave it to me.
It must've dropped out
when we were here this morning.
Can you prove it in some way?
- I mean, is her name on the tag?
- It's hers!
- Is there a receipt?
- It's hers.
Can I see it, please?
Yes. Just, gentle...
Gentle.
Is this her blood too?
It's... It's my blood.
It's my blood from my head
when we fell into the pit.
You know that.
Look, with a head injury....
it's not uncommon to be confused
or to mix things up,
and you're obviously confused.
No, no, no.
Why would I have my daughter's scarf
and not her?
And this is her scarf
'cause she had it in the car
when we were coming back
from Thanksgiving,
and she wanted some batteries,
so we stopped in a service station.
She fell, she went in the hole,
and I fell in on top of her,
and that's where she got the blood.
And then we came here
because she had a broken arm, and she...
We saw you and...
Stop! Get your shit together, man,
or you going to jail!
Do you understand?
You understand? Get it together.
Hello, Ray.
I'm Dr. Teresa Jacobs.
I work in the psychiatric department
for the county.
You're a shrink?
I prefer "medical counselor," but...
"shrink," sure.
I am not crazy.
No one is saying that you are.
I'd like to help you find out
what happened to Joanne and Peri.
We're as concerned about them as you are.
- I doubt that.
- You should think about listening, man.
Officer, thank you. I can handle this now.
You want to come somewhere more private
and talk about this?
Yeah.
Good.
Come on, then.
So, I thought you might be happy to know
they found your admissions file.
Yeah.
Oh, finally.
It's, um, your file,
Ray, not your daughter's.
There's no mention of Peri in here.
No, it's just bullshit
that they just made up.
I was hoping you could talk a bit
about what happened
before the car accident.
It wasn't a car accident.
She fell at a construction site.
Okay, sorry, I only know what's in here.
Maybe you could tell me
what you remember.
I remember everything.
Don't treat me like I'm crazy.
I am treating you
as a rational human being, Ray.
Right now, all I've got to go on
is your word that they were here at all.
There's this.
This proves that they were here...
and that they are hiding them.
He's just hiding everything...
Hiding... what?
That your wife and little girl came in
at random for treatment?
Why would we do that?
Oh, you work here, you tell me.
Tell me about Abby.
She was your first wife?
It's not got anything to do with Abby.
- And she died?
- Yeah.
Eight years ago.
Why don't you tell me what happened?
It was an accident.
She...
It was a head-on collision.
Car accident?
Yeah.
This has nothing to do with this...
or my family now.
In the file,
you mentioned a drinking problem.
That day, Ray,
had you been drinking?
Ray! Ray!
When the accident happened, Ray,
were you too drunk to help Abby?
You didn't even see.
You didn't see it.
Nothing could help her.
I couldn't.
Have you ever had blackouts, Ray?
- Moments of missing time?
- Oh, God.
I don't drink. I don't drink anymore.
- I haven't had a drink in eight years.
- Why...
did you tell the staff
that you were waiting for Abby, Ray?
Help me understand all this.
Abby died
in a car accident eight years ago,
and it kills me.
Every day. It just...
All right.
I'm gonna say something,
and it's gonna be hard to hear.
But you have to listen, Ray,
because I believe you.
I believe something happened
to Peri and Joanne...
Which is why...
I think we should take a look at the spot
where Peri had her accident.
Why? There's nothing there.
I think it's a good idea, Ray.
If you'll excuse me for a moment, hmm?
He's obviously experiencing
some deep trauma.
He's confused.
I suggest going back to the place
he claims his daughter was hurt.
What are you thinking?
They might still be out there.
Oh, God.
I'll, uh, put a call into the canine unit
and see if they can meet us
- at the gas station.
- Mm-hmm.
The place is closed,
but I've got dispatch
trying to track down the cashier.
Um, it might be good for us
if you come along.
- Of course.
- They're not out there.
Maybe you're all in on this,
or maybe you're not.
The fact is, my wife and daughter
went down a hallway in this hospital
and never came back,
and that's what happened.
Is that it, up ahead?
Yeah.
Thanks for coming so quickly.
No problem. What have you got?
Two missing persons,
a woman and child.
You got an incident site?
Ray, where did your daughter fall?
Got a scent source for Mandy?
Can I see that scarf, Ray?
The only thing that dog's gonna smell
is that we were here earlier.
We have to start somewhere, Ray.
Mandy, find.
Good girl. Good girl.
- What happened here, Ray?
- Nothing.
Just, Peri lost a compact, you know?
This tiny toy mirror,
and she was upset, so...
me and Jo, we looked for it.
She looked in the bathroom,
I looked in the car, and then...
and I lost sight of her for a second.
And I look up,
and there's this dog growlin' at her,
and she spooked and fell.
It was nothing.
Here we go.
I think she's got something.
We got something.
Come on.
Let me see it.
Let me see it. Please.
Please. Just give that to me.
It's Peri's. That's what Peri lost.
Please, that's Peri's compact.
Must have just been in her pocket
the whole time,
and it just fell out when she fell.
And the blood?
That's your daughter's blood?
It's my blood. I hit my head.
- Oh, it's yours? You hit your head.
- Yeah.
That's way too much blood!
That's my blood.
I hit my head, man, look at...
- Look! Look at it!
- Get the fuck off me, you crazy fuck!
- Hey!
- No more.
This is a crime scene now.
- Go call the CSI unit.
- Fuckin' nuts, man.
Keep on looking.
There might be more.
He planted it. He planted the mirror!
He planted it.
Did he plant the blood too?
Maybe you did!
- Really?
- Officer. Just give us a second here.
You gotta help me.
You see what's happening here?
- You gotta help me.
- I am trying to help you, Ray.
Now, I asked you once before.
Let me ask you again...
what happened before the accident?
Were you upset about something?
U-Upset at your daughter, maybe?
I was...
I had a fight with my wife
about my marriage.
So, I know that she's not happy.
I know that she just wants me
to try harder. And I do try hard!
I told Peri, "Just stay there." Right?
"Just stay right there."
And she didn't listen,
and she should have listened!
So you were angry with her.
Yeah, I was angry.
I picked up a rock, and I threw it.
At who?
At... At the dog.
I tried hard.
I tried really hard
to... to... to-to grab her.
She still fell.
Ray...
are you sure there was a dog?
There was no dog, was there, Ray?
There was no accident.
Peri didn't fall.
You made that all up.
It happened!
It's... That's all that happened.
Think, Ray.
You were upset at your daughter,
angry at your wife,
angry at yourself.
So you picked up a rock.
When it was over,
you were so angry at yourself
at what you'd done...
Then Joanne appears.
Ray!
So you... lash out.
No! No!
That's what happened, isn't it, Ray?
- Are you hurt?
- The mind, Ray,
it can sometimes create
an alternate reality, a false reality,
to shield itself from trauma.
From the things we fear,
from the horrors we can't even imagine.
Is it broken?
You lost your family once before,
and when you saw
what you'd done to Peri...
and then Joanne,
your mind couldn't accept the fact
that it had happened all over again.
And at your hands.
I would never hurt you, sweetie.
Where are they, Ray?
Where are Peri and Joanne?
Where did you put them?
Ray?
Stand up, Mr. Monroe.
Stand up, Mr. Monroe!
Stand up.
Get up, right now.
Mr. Monroe, you are under arrest
for the suspicion of murder.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will
be used against you in a court of law.
You have the right to an attorney.
If you can not afford an attorney,
one will be provided for you...
Daddy!
Don't move.
It's going to be okay.
I'm just gonna scare him.
Daddy!
No!
Are you hurt?
I don't think so.
It happened.
No, Ray!
Put it down. Put it down.
Put down all your guns.
- Okay...
- Do it now. Now!
Now!
Put down your guns and your radios
and kick 'em away.
- You too!
- You know you're fucking yourself, right?
You stay up there. Right.
Now, everybody up. Everybody out!
You go, get out! Go on, go up!
Everybody up!
I know you won't hurt me, Ray.
You think that I've murdered my wife
and my daughter.
So who are you to me?
Now move it.
Move!
Come on, round the side.
Now open that door.
All right, now get in. Everyone in.
Come on. Come on.
All right.
- Give me your key card.
- Ray...
if you thought seeing that dog
somehow makes everything else
you believe true,
you are wrong.
Or you're wrong.
Give me the card.
- Mistake.
- Well, we'll see.
You motherfucker!
You motherfucker! You're so fucked!
I'm coming for you.
- Still seeing Phil from radiology?
- I don't think so.
Ah.
I tell you, Terry,
what a long day that was.
Pretty crazy, huh?
I mean,
I'm afraid to even pick mine up, you know?
What if I drop him?
So, is this your first?
Ray, watch out!
Sorry, Mr. Monroe. She's gone.
They're both gone.
That's it. Call it.
I'm sorry, Mr. Monroe. They're gone.
Abby...
Do something.
Hey.
Eighty-two degrees.
Heads up.
Help me. Help me.
Help me, please.
Help.
Doctor? Doctor!
Sign in, please.
Thank you. Good work.
Come on... Come on.
Oh, fuck...
Go!
Just... Just...
stop.
Just stop.
I just want to get my family...
and I want to go home.
Just point the barrel away. All right?
Okay.
I'll take you to your family, all right?
They're right downstairs.
Thirty seconds away.
Give me...
Give me the keys.
Yeah.
Okay.
This is over!
Give me my family!
I hope you feel better.
EMS just brought in
a couple head traumas.
Head-on collision. Drunk driver.
The most beautiful eyes I've ever seen.
Would you like Peri listed
for organ donation?
No.
Can I convince you to reconsider?
Don't touch her!
Get back! Away from the table.
Put that down! Put it down!
Back against the wall! Peri...
Peri? Stay there.
Oh...
Take off your mask.
Take it off.
You're a monster.
You're all monsters.
Ray, don't do this.
Don't worry, baby. I got you, baby.
You don't need to do this.
- Ray... Ray...
- Jo?
Jo! Jo! Jo! Jo!
No.
Ray... Ray...
- Come on. Come on.
- Ray...
You think you can cut up my family?
You think you can just cut up
my little girl?
Put the gun away.
Nobody needs to get hurt.
Daddy's here.
Ray, you are deeply confused.
I'm not afraid of you.
Ray, don't do this, please.
Ray... Ray...
They drugged us.
I know. Hold on to Peri.
Ray.
You're not seeing things clearly.
I've never felt more clear.
Come on, come on.
Hold him down!
Propofol, 15 milligrams!
Ray!
Oh, Jo, you're okay!
You're okay.
I got you. I got you.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Stop! Stop! Stop!
- Whoa, whoa!
Just get out of my way.
Mr. Monroe, listen to me.
You gotta listen to me.
We can't let you leave.
You can't leave here.
You remember me?
I'm Dr. Bruce Volk. Do you remember?
Look, we just want to help you.
Why don't you just put the gun down...
Fuck! Shit!
I did it.
Yeah, I did it.
You fucking shot me!
I did it.
Fuck you!
We're nearly there.
Here you go. Stay warm.
Daddy?
Yeah?
Are we home yet?
Soon, sweetheart.
Soon.
You okay?
We are now.
My arm, Daddy, it still hurts.
Well, how about a song,
will that make you feel better?
Mm-hmm.
♪ Red and yellow and pink and green ♪
♪ Purple and orange and blue ♪
♪ I can sing a rainbow ♪
♪ Sing a rainbow ♪
♪ Sing a rainbow for you ♪
Don't touch her!
Peri!
Ray.
You're not seeing things clearly.
I got you. I got you.
You're not thinking clearly.
You're deeply confused.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Stop!
- Stop!
- You're deeply confused.
- The mind, Ray...
No!
Can sometimes create
an alternate reality,
a false reality...
to shield itself from trauma.
From the things we fear.
From the horrors we can't imagine.
Daddy.
Oh, my God!
She's okay. She's okay. She's okay!
- Where's Daddy?
- She's okay. She's okay.
Okay. Okay.
♪ Sing a rainbow ♪
♪ Sing a rainbow for you ♪
How was that?
Good.
Let's go home.